A Guide to the Carol Barton Papers, 1973-2015: SC 0274
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 3: Ephemera and Personal Papers, 1979-2013
  Series 3: Ephemera and Personal Papers, 1979-2013, contains personal papers and ephemera Barton received and collected over the course of her career. Her personal papers include correspondence between friends, colleagues, students, and galleries. The ephemeral items include awards and items of personal interests such as flip-books, magnets, promotional pop-ups, etc.
  - Correspondence, 1979-1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Moveable Beasts, Melanie Runcie finals dissertation, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Book publication ephemera, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ker-Bloom! ephemera, 1996-2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Marketplace audio tapes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 10th Hands On Pop-up & Movable Book Exhibit with signature, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Comics, 1999, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Honors and awards, 2008-2013 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Letter from President Barack Obama and Inauguration of President Obama pin, 2009-2012 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - National Geographic photographs and press, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Frankfurt Fair Proposal slides, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Cyanotype Pop-up, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)